Guide to the Henry Solon Graves Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Henry Solon Graves papers
1877-1952
MS 249
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
23
(53 boxes)
The papers consist of correspondence, writings, diaries, notes, photographs, and other papers relating to the personal life and professional career of Henry Solon Graves. The collection documents Graves' academic and administrative career, his professional writings and activities, and his service during World War I as a forestry engineer in France.
Graves, Henry Solon, 1871-1951
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the Yale Forestry School Archives, 1963.
Arrangement
Arranged in three series: I. Correspondence, 1896-1952. II. Topical Files, 1877-1951. III. Printed Material, 1903-1951.
Scope and Contents
The papers consist of correspondence, writings, diaries, notes, photographs, and other papers relating to the personal life and professional career of Henry Solon Graves, a forester who served as the first director of the Yale University School of Forestry (1900-1910), the chief forester for the United States Department of Agriculture (1910-1920), Sterling Professor of Forestry and Dean of the School of Forestry, and provost of the university (1923-1927.) The collection documents Graves' academic and administrative career, his professional writings and activities, and his service during World War I as a forestry engineer in France.
The papers are arranged in fifty-three (53) boxes totaling 23 linear feet. Span dates for the collection are 1877-1952, and the papers are arranged in three series: I. CORRESPONDENCE, 1896-1952; II. TOPICAL FILES, 1877-1951; III. PRINTED MATERIAL, 1903-1951.
SERIES I, CORRESPONDENCE, 1896-1952, contains letters relating to Graves' Yale University responsibilities as an educator and administrator and as a prominent national figure in the fields of forestry, conservation, and education. Individual correspondents include: Gifford Pinchot, William Howard Taft, and Theodore Roosevelt. Important correspondence is also arranged under topical headings established by Graves, including: American Forestry Association, Educational Planning, General Education Board, and Personal. Graves corresponded with several university figures in the course of his career, and also with many individuals and organizations active in the fields of forestry and conservation.
SERIES II, TOPICAL FILES, 1877-1951, contains correspondence, writings, diaries, photographs, and other papers relating to Graves' professional career. Examples of Graves' writings are arranged in "Addresses and articles" (folders 174-179) and "Writings" (folders 524-525). A more complete selection of writings are arranged in SERIES III.
Grave's role in formulating and advocating national forestry policy and legislation is reflected in files organized under the headings "Bills" (folders 188-207), "Forest policy" (folders 281-301), "Grazing" (folders 323-330), "Policy" (folders 430-432),"Public domain" (folders 436-441), and others.
Diaries (folders 223-247) consist of several volumes of notes compiled by Graves from 1914-1948, including items relating to Alaska, an Education Study, Field notes, India, and other trips and projects. Lecture notes (folders 343-372) contain notes on several lectures relating to forestry and conservation topics such as forest economics, Indian lands, and taxation.
Photographs (folders 405-429) document many of Graves' travels around the world, including trips to Alaska, India, Cuba, and the Philippines. Other topics represented in this series include: Forest services, Forestry services, Land, Lumber code, Parks, Railroads, Redwood League, Timber Conservation Board, and World War I.
SERIES, PRINTED MATERIAL, 1903-1951, consists of bound volumes of typescripts. The articles, speeches, essays, and reports contained in these volumes include many writings which were published. The volumes contain a group of papers arranged in chronological order (volumes 1-4), a group of papers relating to national forests arranged by state, and other papers.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Henry Solon Graves was born on May 3, 1871 in Marietta, Ohio. He was a forester and organized the School of Forestry at Yale University. Graves died in Brattleboro, Vermont on March 7, 1951. Graves attended Yale University (B.A. 1892, M.A. 1900), Harvard University, and the University of Munich, Germany. From 1900-1910, he was director of the Yale Forestry School. Graves was chief forester of the U.S. Department of Agriculture from 1910-1920. In 1923 he returned to Yale University, where he was dean of the School of Forestry (1923-1939) and provost of the University (1923-1927). He retired as dean emeritus in 1939.
Conservation of natural resources; Environmental protection; Forestry schools and education; Forests and forestry -- Measurement; Lumbering; World War, 1914-1918 -- France; Autobiographies; Diaries; Educators; Foresters; Graves, Henry Solon, 1871-1951; Olmsted, Frederick Law, 1870-1957; Pershing, John J. (John Joseph), 1860-1948; Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919; Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930; American Forestry Association; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University. School of Forestry
- Correspondence, 1896-1952; Series I; 5.5 linear feet (13 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence arranged alphabetically by the name of the individual correspondent and/or topic.
  - A (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Forestry Association, 1935-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2-9)
  - B (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Berry Schools, 1939-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bonbright, Irving W., 1929-1934 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - C (Box 2, Folder 13-19)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1928-1930 (Box 2, Folder 20-22)
  - Chapman, H.H., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - China, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - D (Box 2, Folder 25-26)
  - D (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Davenport College, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Dissenters, 1942-1946 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Draft boards, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Duke and Georgia Schools, 1932, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Dwight, Timothy (College), 1931-1945 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
  - E (Box 3, Folder 34-35)
  - Education, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 36-38)
  - Education in the South, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Educational Planning, 1933-1936 (Box 3, Folder 40-42)
  - Educational Planning, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 43-46)
  - F, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 47-49)
  - Forest conditions, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Forest economics, 1938-1940 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Forest policy, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Forest services, 1913, 1935-1939 (Box 4, Folder 53-56)
  - France: World War I, 1914-1918, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - French: newspapers, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - G, 1941-1950 (Box 5, Folder 59-60)
  - General Education Board, 1940, 1942-1944 (Box 5, Folder 61-62)
  - Graduate Advisory Board, 1900-1912 (Box 6, Folder 63-69)
  - Graduate Advisory Board, 1913-1919 (Box 7, Folder 70-85)
  - Graduate Advisory Board, undated (Box 8, Folder 86-87)
  - H, 1920, 1940-1946, 1949-1952 (Box 8, Folder 88-92)
  - I, 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - J, 1928-1929, 1942-1949 (Box 8, Folder 94-95)
  - Joint Committee Report, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Joint Research Council, 1942-1946 (Box 8, Folder 97-99)
  - K, 1941-1947 (Box 8, Folder 100-101)
  - L, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Legislation, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 103-104)
  - M, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 105-107)
  - Mc, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 108-109)
  - Mason, D.T., 1943 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Munger, T.T., 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - N, 1942-1949 (Box 9, Folder 112-113)
  - National Arboretum, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - O, 1911-1949 (Box 9, Folder 115-117)
  - P, 1919-1943 (Box 9, Folder 118-121)
  - Personal, 1896-1898; 1919-1825 (Box 10, Folder 122-126)
  - Pinchot, Gifford, 1904, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - R, 1920, 1942, 1945-1949 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Retirement, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - S, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 131-135)
  - S (Box 11, Folder 135-136)
  - Sargent, Charles Sprague, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Smith, Herbert, 1936-1944 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - T, 1943-1950 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Taft, William Howard, 1910; 1917 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - U, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - University business (Box 11, Folder 142-144)
  - V, 1936-1948 (Box 11, Folder 145-146)
  - W, 1940-1950 (Box 11, Folder 147-148)
  - Washington, D.C., 1943-1946 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Y, 1923, 1946-1949 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Miscellanea, 1903-1945 (Box 12, Folder 151-163)
  - Miscellanea, 1946-1951 (Box 13, Folder 164-172)
- Topical Files, 1877-1951; Series II; 14.5 linear feet (35 boxes)
  This series contains files arranged alphabetically by the name of the topic, individual or organization.
  - Acquisitions, 1935, undated (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Addresses and articles, 1921-1946 (Box 14, Folder 174-179)
  - Adirondacks, 1905-1938 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Agricultural policy, 1934-1937 (Box 15, Folder 181)
  - Alaska, 1911-1921 (Box 15, Folder 182-183)
  - American Forestry Association, 1939-1941 (Box 15, Folder 184-185)
  - Arboretum, National, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 186)
  - Arkansas, undated (Box 15, Folder 187)
  - Bank, First of New Haven, 1939-1943 (Box 15, Folder 187)
  - Bills
    - Capper resolution data, 1919-1922, undated (Box 15, Folder 188-192)
    - Coal Act and Congressional bill, 1920-1928, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 193)
    - Federal aid, 1921-1926 (Box 16, Folder 194-195)
    - Forest devastation, 1923-1925 (Box 16, Folder 196)
    - Forest restoration, 1939-1940 (Box 16, Folder 197)
    - Forestry conservation, 1920-1928 (Box 16, Folder 198)
    - General, 1920-1935 (Box 16, Folder 199-200)
    - Land laws, undated (Box 17, Folder 201)
    - McNary-Doxey, 1936-1938 (Box 17, Folder 202)
    - New York laws, 1923, 1928-1936 (Box 17, Folder 203)
    - Omnibus, 1935-1936 (Box 17, Folder 204)
    - Oregon-California grant, 1936-1939, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 205)
    - Miscellanea, 1897, 1921-1935 (Box 17, Folder 206-207)
  - Biographical Notes
    - History of Forestry, 1905-1906, 1949, undated (Box 17, Folder 208-211)
    - History of Forestry, 1898, 1928, 1943, 1946, undated (Box 18, Folder 212-214)
    - Miscellanea, undated (Box 18, Folder 215-217)
  - Botany, Institute of, 1931 undated (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - Bryant, Ralph Clement, 1877, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Connecticut Rural Homes Plan, 1933, undated (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Cooperatives, Reports on Breathitt County, 1948, undated (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - Courses, 1939, 1943, undated (Box 19, Folder 222)
  - Diaries
    - General, 1914-1918, 1929, 1933, 1936, 1941-1942, 1945, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 223-232)
    - Alaska, 1914-1915 (Box 19, Folder 233)
    - Alaska, undated (Box 20, Folder 234)
    - Anecdotes, undated (Box 20, Folder 235)
    - Education study, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 236)
    - Field Notes, 1910, 1913-1919, 1939-1940, undated (Box 20, Folder 237-240)
    - India, 1904-1905 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - Redwoods, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 242)
    - Western trip, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 243)
    - World War I, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 244)
    - Miscellanea, 1936, 1939, 1940-1948, undated (Box 21, Folder 245-247)
  - Dissenters, 1927-1935, 1939, 1940-1941, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 248-251)
  - Education
    - General Board, 1920-1941 (Box 22, Folder 252-254)
    - Park Board, 1936-1938, undated (Box 22, Folder 255-259)
    - South Report, 1938-1940, undated (Box 22, Folder 260)
  - Education in forestry, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 261-262)
  - Erosion, 1933-1939, undated (Box 22, Folder 263-264)
  - Erosion and flood control (Box 23, Folder 265)
  - Escambia River: Eichburg case, 1921 undated (Box 23, Folder 266-268)
  - Food and Agriculture
    - Time Report, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 269)
    - United Nations, 1941-1948, undated (Box 23, Folder 270-273)
    - Forest credits, 1921-1942 (Box 24, Folder 274-276)
  - Forest economics and policy, 1929-1942 (Box 24, Folder 277-279)
  - Forest education; forest fires, 1918, 1921, 1927-1929 (Box 24, Folder 280)
  - Forest policy, 1897, 1916-1928
    - General, 1897, 1916-1928 (Box 24, Folder 281-284)
    - General, 1929-1938 (Box 25, Folder 285-290)
    - Fire protection, 1919-1929 (Box 25, Folder 291)
    - National, 1912-1924 (Box 25, Folder 292)
    - New York, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 293)
    - Notes and outlines, 1928-1939 (Box 25, Folder 294-295)
    - Statements, 1905-1908 (Box 26, Folder 296-298)
    - Title 1-9, 1909-1934nd (Box 26, Folder 299-300)
    - Title 10 and 11, 1920, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 301)
  - Forest Services
    - General, 1902-1906 (Box 26, Folder 302-304)
    - General, 1920-1949 (Box 27, Folder 305-307)
    - Criticisms of U.S. Forest Services, 1910 (Box 27, Folder 308)
    - District Forester's Meeting, 1916 (Box 27, Folder 309)
  - Forestry Conservation Committee, 1936-1941 (Box 27, Folder 310-311)
  - Forestry Conservation: newspaper clippings, 1919-1920 (Box 28, Folder 312)
  - Forestry Depletion Economic outline, 1938-1940 (Box 28, Folder 313)
  - Forestry Services
    - France, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 314)
    - Organization chart, 1942, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 315)
    - Statistics, 1935, 1938-1947 (Box 28, Folder 316-317)
  - Forestry survey, 1933-1941 (Box 28, Folder 318)
  - Forestry and war, undated (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - Forests, 1945, undated (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Game and wild fowl refuges, 1929, 1932-1935 (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - Geological timetable, 1926-1949 (Box 28, Folder 322)
  - Grazing
    - General, 1892-1926, undated (Box 29, Folder 323-324)
    - Bills and other printed material, 1925-1926, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 325)
    - Controversy, 1926-1927 (Box 29, Folder 326-329)
    - Policy, 1926, 1934-1935 (Box 29, Folder 330)
  - Gregg, William C., 1925 (Box 29, Folder 331)
  - Harriman estate, 1902, 1914-1916, 1939-1940 (Box 29, Folder 332)
  - Hoover's policy, 1929-1930 (Box 30, Folder 333)
  - Hurricane and tornado, 1938, undated (Box 30, Folder 334-336)
  - Ickes bill, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 337-338)
  - Land
    - Exchange, 1912-1915; 1928 (Box 30, Folder 339)
    - Pressure, 1947, undated (Box 30, Folder 340-341)
    - Use, 1912-1947 (Box 31, Folder 342)
  - Lecture notes:
    - Cooperative land use, 1938-1939 (Box 31, Folder 343)
    - Economics I-V, 1938-1939 (Box 31, Folder 344)
    - Economics II, 1930-1939, undated (Box 31, Folder 345-346)
    - Federal and state relations, 1938-1940 (Box 31, Folder 347)
    - Forest economics, 1935-1940, undated (Box 31, Folder 348-352)
    - Forest fires, undated (Box 31, Folder 353)
    - Forest laws, 1880-1885; 1913-1915 (Box 31, Folder 354)
    - Forest policy, 1927-1942, undated (Box 32, Folder 355-359)
    - Grazing, 1939, undated (Box 32, Folder 360)
    - History, undated (Box 32, Folder 361)
    - Indian land, 1934, 1936, undated (Box 32, Folder 362)
    - Sustained field, 1935-1936 (Box 32, Folder 363)
    - Taxation, 1915, 1930-1934, undated (Box 32, Folder 364-366)
    - Tax delinquent lands, 1928-1938 (Box 33, Folder 367)
  - Lecture Notes
    - Water conservation, 1938, undated (Box 33, Folder 368)
    - Miscellaneous, 1922-1944, undated (Box 33, Folder 369-372)
  - Lumber code, 1933-1934, undated (Box 33, Folder 373-378)
  - Lumber code, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 379-380)
  - Maps, 1926-1939, undated (Box 34, Folder 381-382)
  - Mississippi Valley, 1927, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 383-384)
  - National Forestry Areas Panels, 1915-1946 (Box 34, Folder 385-386)
  - National Research Council & Society of American Foresters, 1942-1943, undated (Box 34, Folder 387-388)
  - Oastler F.R., undated (Box 35, Folder 389)
  - Ohio basin, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 390)
  - Pack, Charles Lanthop, 1912-1943, undated (Box 35, Folder 391-396)
  - Parks
    - National, 1922-1939, undated (Box 35, Folder 397-398)
    - New Haven Commission, 1933-1942 (Box 36, Folder 399)
    - State, 1925-1927 (Box 36, Folder 400-40l)
  - Passports, 1904-1917 (Box 36, Folder 402)
  - Personnel - methods of judging, 1931 (Box 36, Folder 403)
  - Philippine report, 1905 (Box 36, Folder 404)
  - Photographs
    - General, undated (Box 36, Folder 405-409)
    - Alaska trip, 1915 (Box 37, Folder 410)
    - British India and California, undated (Box 37, Folder 411)
    - Conservation of Our Nation Resources, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 412)
    - Cuba, undated (Box 37, Folder 413)
    - Floods and erosion, undated (Box 37, Folder 414)
    - India (and Philippines), undated (Box 37, Folder 415)
    - Insect Studies, forest, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 416)
    - Personal, undated (Box 37, Folder 417-419)
    - Philippines, undated (Box 37, Folder 420)
    - Timber frauds, 1914, undated (Box 38, Folder 421-424)
    - U.S.A. West, undated (Box 38, Folder 425-426)
    - Western trip, 1937 (Box 38, Folder 427-428)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - Policy
    - Laws I, as dated (Box 39, Folder 430)
    - Laws II, as dated (Box 39, Folder 431)
    - Old laws, as dated (Box 39, Folder 432)
  - Preserves, national, 1932, 1939-1940, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 433)
  - Public control, 1944-1945, undated (Box 39, Folder 434)
  - Public cooperation, 1938-1939, undated (Box 39, Folder 435)
  - Public domain
    - General, 1910, 1928-1934, undated (Box 39, Folder 436-439)
    - Legislation, 1931-1932 (Box 39, Folder 440)
    - Scrip, free homestead, military bounty, undated (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - Public land, undated (Box 40, Folder 442)
  - Railroads
    - Fires, 1910-1927 (Box 40, Folder 443-444)
    - Woods, 1919-1920 (Box 40, Folder 445)
  - Reclamation, 1922-1923 (Box 40, Folder 446)
  - Recreation, 1922-1935 (Box 40, Folder 447-448)
  - Redwood League
    - Correspondence, 1923-1926 (Box 40, Folder 449-452)
    - Correspondence, 1926-1944 (Box 41, Folder 453-456)
    - Maps, 1921-1948, undated (Box 41, Folder 457-460)
    - Minutes and memorandums, 1927, 1944-1947 (Box 41, Folder 461)
    - Pacific Lumber Company, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 462)
    - Photos, 1922-1927, 1939-1944 (Box 42, Folder 463)
  - Regulations committee, 1934-1935 (Box 42, Folder 464)
  - Reorganization, 1932, 1937-1938 (Box 42, Folder 465-468)
  - Reorganization bill, 1937-1938 (Box 42, Folder 469-470)
  - Reorganization correspondence, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 471)
  - Reports, 1940, 1945, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 472)
  - Research, state, 1942, undated (Box 43, Folder 473)
  - Scholarship: Inter American Trade, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 474)
  - Seymour, George Dudley, 1915-1945 (Box 43, Folder 475-477)
  - Shelterbelt: Slattery, Harry A., 1932-1938k (Box 43, Folder 478)
  - Smith, Herbert A., 1929-1939 (Box 43, Folder 479-480)
  - Society of American Foresters, 1922-1945, 1950-1951 (Box 43, Folder 481-482)
  - State Forestry Administration, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 483)
  - Taylor Grazing Act, 1934, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 484)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority: bills, 1936-1938 (Box 44, Folder 485)
  - Timber Conservation Board
    - General, 1930-1931 (Box 44, Folder 486-493)
    - General, 1931-1948 (Box 45, Folder 494-496)
    - Correspondence, 1906-1916, 1925 (Box 45, Folder 497)
  - Timber ownership (Box 45, Folder 498)
  - Timber Salvage Commission (Mass.), 1939 (Box 45, Folder 499)
  - Trees of New Haven, undated (Box 45, Folder 500)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1910-1911, 1917-1918 (Box 45, Folder 501)
  - Wage hour law, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 502)
  - Water control, 1910-1912, 1933, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 503)
  - Water pollution, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 504-505)
  - Weyerhaeuser, 1942-1943 (Box 46, Folder 506)
  - Wildlife, 1912-1938 (Box 46, Folder 507-408)
  - Wing, Leonard William, 1933-1939 (Box 46, Folder 509)
  - Work Camp, 1928-1939 (Box 46, Folder 510)
  - World War I
    - Correspondence, 1917-1923 (Box 46, Folder 511)
    - Forestry reports: France, 1917-1918, undated (Box 46, Folder 512)
    - Papers: France (wood), 1917-1919, undated (Box 46, Folder 513-518)
    - Papers: French forests, 1918 (Box 47, Folder 519)
    - Papers: food exchange, 1918 (Box 47, Folder 520)
    - Printed material, 1918, 1921-1924 (Box 47, Folder 521)
    - Promotions, 1917-1941 (Box 47, Folder 522-523)
  - Writings: "Education and Research in Forestry", 1940 (Box 47, Folder 524)
  - Writings: "Forest conditions in Cuba", undated (Box 47, Folder 525)
  - Yale Forestry School, 1910, 1926-1930, 1945-1946 (Box 47, Folder 526)
  - Miscellaneous, 1900-1948 (Box 48, Folder 527-532)
- Printed Material, 1903-1951; Series III; 2 linear feet (5 boxes)
  This series contains material arranged by volume number, with unnumbered items filed at the end of the series.
  - Papers and articles
    - Vol. 1 and 2, 1909-1916 (Box 49, Folder 533-534)
    - Vol. 3 and 4, 1917-1926 (Box 50, Folder 535-536)
  - Our Public Lands and Forest Policy: Vol. 5, 1951
    General
    See: box 53, folder 545
  - Papers
    - Vol. 6, 1915-1945 (Box 51, Folder 537)
    - National forests
      - Vol. 7 Alaska-Arkansas, 1905-1910 (Box 51, Folder 538)
      - Vol. 8-9 California, 1903-1904 (Box 51, Folder 539-540)
      - Vol. 10 Colorado-Wyoming, 1905-1907 (Box 52, Folder 541)
      - Vol. 11 New Mexico-Utah (Box 52, Folder 542)
      - Vol. 12 Oregon-Washington; Timber sales, 1905-1910 (Box 52, Folder 543)
  - Papers and Reports, 1903-1947 (Box 53, Folder 544)
  - Our Public Lands … Vol. 5, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 545)